Contact

bkeaton04@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/brittanykeaton-msn-fnp-c-aaa557103 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Acute Care Critical Care ACLS

Languages

English

Certifications

BSN,MSN, CCRN, FCCS, ENPC, BLS Instructor, ACLS Instructor

Brittany Keaton MSN, FNP-C

Nurse Practitioner

Fort Worth, Texas

Summary

Nurse Practitioner with a demonstrated history of working in the Hospital & Health Care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Patient Safety, Healthcare Information Technology (HIT), and Acute Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's Degree focused in Family Nurse Practitioner from Chamberlain College of Nursing.

Experience

DALLAS RENAL GROUP, P.A.
Nurse Practitioner
March 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Nephrology

Texas Health Resources Registered Nurse

Texas Health Resources
Critical Care RN/CV Clinician/Dialysis
December 2011 - February 2017 (5 years 3 months)
Texas

Plaza Medical Center Critical Care RN June 2008 - December 2011 (3 years 7 months) Texas

RPNT

Acute Care Dialysis RN 2010 - 2011 (1 year) Texas

Education

Chamberlain College of Nursing
Master's Degree, Family Nurse Practitioner · (2014 - 2016)

Texas Woman's University
Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing
Research and Clinical Nursing · (2004 - 2008)